[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Chang Huan.
We're here.
[Apocalypse Log 13]
Did you sleep well last night?
Yeah.
Not again.
It's split open.
I'm talking about your wound.
What were you thinking?
It's fine.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
The fever's gone, too.
Let's focus on the task at hand.
He Yao took the car.
What do we do now?
Follow the highway.
We should be able to find a working car.
Let's go.
Watch your step.
What's wrong? Did the wound open again?
So childish.
So what?
What can do about it?
You're such a child.
This place...
is actually quite well-preserved.
Yeah.
Let's take a break.
For a split second there,
I thought I was back before the apocalypse.
It felt like...
this was just a normal date.
Did you use to come to places like this?
Do you mean on a date, or to see a performance?
This is my first date.
I rarely came to live shows.
Have you ever experienced this before?
Let's eat first.
You're so lazy.
Here...
It's okay.
We're adequately far away.
I didn't expect zombies to still have skills from when they were alive.
Do you think...
zombies might still have a shred of human consciousness left?
Is it possible that one day,
zombies could turn back into humans?
It's just muscle memory.
A zombie is a zombie.
They can't turn back.
Where are we?
He Yao.
What exactly are you trying to do?
Stop feeding me these useless things.
There's no going back.
I know my own condition.
I have a plan.
Just give me some time.
The equipment here may be old,
but it's still functional.
He Yao, you're always like this.
Always acting like you're in total control.
But when have you ever cared about what others think?
Do you have any idea?
The way you're acting now...
is just like when you first barged into my life.
Leave.
Just get out of here.
I don't want to see you.
Yao Yao.
This will be your home from now on.
Don't be a stranger.
Chang Huan is back.
Come here.
This is your brother, He Yao.
You've met before.
You remember him, right?
He'll be living with us from now on.
Yeah, I know.
I'm going to my room.
Your bed...
Chang Huan is a bit shy around strangers.
Mom.
Chang Huan, you're back. Give that to me.
What do you want to eat? I'll cook it.
Today, I want to eat...
Yao Yao.
What happened to you?
How did you cut your head?
Come here and sit down.
I'll clean the wound for you.
It's okay, Auntie.
I just fell by accident.
But your head is bleeding.
How did you manage to do this?
How could you be so careless?
I'm fine, Auntie.
Let me dab it again.
I'll be gentle.
You're so careless. Let's use a new one.
Your dad is working overtime.
Let's eat first.
Come on, eat more.
Here.
Today, Mr. Wang called me specifically
to say that for the midterms,
the top two in the grade are in our house.
I'm so happy.
Auntie, Chang Huan is the amazing one.
For that tough math problem this time,
his solution was very unique.
Even the teacher didn't think of it.
Really?
You are both my pride and joy.
Auntie, Chang Huan and I will keep up the good work.
I'm full.
This time, I didn't do well.
Chang Huan! Chang Huan!
What's wrong with this child?
Do you want some water?
Drinking too much water at night
is bad for your kidneys.
Still studying at this hour?
Is it for the Math Olympiad?
This problem of yours...
I'll study on my own.
Ever since we were kids,
I've been trying my hardest,
but I'm always one step behind you.
He Yao.
In your eyes, will I always need to be taken care of?
You're my brother.
Of course I have to take care of you.
I'm not your brother.
I am Sheng Chang Huan.
I don't care what you think.
You...
Since we're tied together now,
this path...
we must walk it together.
Leaving me is not an option.
It never was.
The inflammation in your wound is getting worse.
We need to find some anti-inflammatory medicine soon.
Rest for a bit.
Wait here and don't move.
I'll check if there's water in the well.
Come back quickly.
Why did you come over here?
I wanted to keep an eye on you.
I told you not to move.
Don't move.
Friends.
Where are you two from?